graphics-illustrations.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy & Cookies - Graphics-Illustrations

This privacy policy sets out how **Graphics-Illustrations**  uses and protects any information that you give **Graphics-Illustrations**  when you use this website.

**Graphics-Illustrations** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Graphics-Illustrations** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from: May 2018

## Privacy Policy www.graphics-illustrations.com

**Last updated: May, 2018**

www.graphics-illustrations.com is a Site publishing design and graphics related articles. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site and the user experience. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we use third party services such as Google Analytics and Amazon AWS Emailing services that collect, monitor and analyze this data to further improve on the overall user experience.

**Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that will help improving the overall user experience. You may opt-out from our mailing list at any time.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@graphics-illustrations.com

### GDPR – General Data Protection Regulations

We embrace the changes brought by the new EU General Data Protection Regulations, and our Privacy Policy intends to reflect the transparency this law requires.

**What data does www.graphics-illustrations.com collect?**

We collect the following data from our users:  
* Email – User email address.  
* Name – Full name, nick name or user name.  
* Password – The password for the account.  
* Website – This is optional.  
* Country – This is optional.

### How we utilize the information collected?

We require user identification in order to better manage the distribution of the copyrighted content offered by our website.

Also, we want to provide our users with the best experience possible when browsing our website. We therefore sometimes send newsletters, marketing or promotional materials regarding content relevant to our users. We DO NOT, and WILL NOT share user information with third parties other than the ones required for normal website functionalities (Google Analytics, Amazon AWS). User information is only accessible and used within the website and group of websites affiliated with www.graphics-illustrations.com.

We ensure that the same strict Privacy Policy constraints apply to affiliated websites. The affiliated websites are controlled and managed by the same www.graphics-illustrations.com staff.

### How is your data stored and secured?

We use the industrie’s standard procedures for ensuring optimal security of the user information we store. Databases are not directly accessible. They are only accessible via our hosting provide. Therefore, access to the databases implies a two-way authentication procedure. Strong passwords are used and regularly changed to further enforce security. Access to the databases is restricted to only www.graphics-illustrations.com technical staff.

All user data is stored with Inmotion Hosting, an award winning hosting provider, inside their data centers located in USA. Inmotion Hosting adheres to the strictest security standards, so your data is safe.

The users have the following rights

**Right of access**

You can ask us what personal data is being processed (used), why and where. To do this, please send your request at info@graphics-illustrations.com from the email address associated with your account.

**Right to rectification**

If you, or your customer, want to correct, revise or remove any of the data we retain on you – as explained in our Privacy Policy – you may do so at any time. To do this, please send your request at info@graphics-illustrations.com from the email address associated with your account.

**Right to be forgotten**

If you, need to cancel your account at any time, we will permanently remove your account and all information associated with it. To do this, please send your request at info@graphics-illustrations.com from the email address associated with your account.

**Right to restrict processing**

If you, believe your personal data is inaccurate or collected unlawfully, you may request limited use of your personal data. To do this, please send your request at info@graphics-illustrations.com from the email address associated with your account.

**Right to object**

If you, decide that you no longer wish to allow your data to be included in our analytics or for us to provide personalized (targeted) marketing content at any time, you may contact us to request removal of this data. You can also do this via the unsubscribe link offered in our newsletter emails.

We will respond to all requests, inquiries or concerns within thirty (30) days.

***

### What is a cookie?

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device.

You can find more information about cookies at:

  * For a video about cookies visit [a look at cookies](http://www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies)

Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. The cookies used on this website have been categorized based on the categories found in the ICC UK Cookie guide.

### Category 1: strictly necessary cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.

### Category 2: performance cookies

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.

By using our website, you agree that we can place these type of cookies on your device.

### Category 3: functionality cookies

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

By using our website, you agree that we can place these type of cookies on your device.

### Category 4: targeting cookies or advertising cookies

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organizations.

A list of all the cookies used on this website by category is set out below.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or [emailing us here](http://graphics-illustrations.com/about/)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.

A small fee will be payable.

If you would like a copy of the information held on you [please write here](http://graphics-illustrations.com/about/)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
